# First Last Python Developer

Certified Python Developer offering 6 years of extensive experience and exceptional analytical and critical thinking skills. Delivers a proactive approach, great work ethic, and the ability to function well in fast-paced/deadline-driven team environments.

San Francisco, CA 12345 +1 234 567-890 first.last@resumeworded.com linkedin.com/in/resumeworded

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Growthsi, New York, NY

## Certified Python Developer

#### January 2020 - Present

- Developed web application back end components while communicating with 30+ clients to identify their needs/goals and work on meeting them.
- Worked on the improvement of data protection and security, increasing security rate by 24 % while creating new user information solutions.
- Maintained large databases and configured services to reduce software maintenance expenses, decreasing the costs by 15% within just one year.
- Trained and supervised 3 employees, providing training support/guidance.
- Obtained the Employee of the Year Award for meeting and exceeding all assigned goals and objectives and contributing to 33% overall success.

# Growthsi, New York, NY

## Python Developer/Tester

#### July 2016 - December 2019

- Successfully automated the moving of 5 tests from production to staging and staging to production by carefully reading the keywords from NVbugs.
- Consumed APIs while utilizing Python requests to read numerous JSON reports and file automatic bugs in the NVBugs for intermittent tests.
- Designed and configured database and backend applications and programs, contributing to operations continuity and increasing efficiency by 14%.
- Developed, tested, and debugged software tools utilized by 100+ clients and internal customers to facilitate and easier process and user experience.
- Obtained adequate experience in reviewing Python code for running the troubleshooting test-cases and bug issues, acquiring all necessary skills.

# Resume Worded, Boston, MA

### Python Developer Intern

#### January 2015 - June 2016

- Designed robust, scalable, secure, and globalized web-based applications to ensure the continuity of all business processes and client satisfaction.
- Used the Python language to develop 3 web-based data retrieval systems.
- Performed data entry and other clerical work for project completion.
- Conducted descriptive and multivariate statistical analysis of data using Matlab, gaining 100% accuracy rate in terms of interpretation and analysis.

#### **SKILLS**

Python

HTML, JavaScript

Selenium

TestComplete

**Appium** 

Frameworks Django

Flask

Pyramid

**PyJamas** 

**Jython** 

Angular JS; Node JS

Spring

WebLogic

WebSphere

JBoss Amazon EC2

Jenkins And Fabric J2EE JDBC

JNDI

JSP And Servlets Databases Oracle MySQL

#### **EDUCATION**

## Resume Worded University

BS Computer Science

November 2014

Boston, MA

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

## Resume Worded University

Certified Python Developer

May 2016

Boston, MA